[Music]
rival gangs the Bloods Crips and the
black gorilla gang calling a truce for
the first time in Baltimore history the
real problem they say Decades of poverty
and police brutality
whoa you know the cops are running wild
when gang leaders start sounding like
gnome Chomsky by
comparison we multiply
Eminem and we add that to W * W for
same-sex marriage
rates okay we divide that by m * W
that's straight marriage rates okay now
we take the derivative t plus M uh
Turtle Man marriage
rate and raise that to the power of a
cubed abortion abortion
abortion okay so far we've got oh
legitimate rap okay I blame gay marriage
for the Lakers playing
horribly uh I will just say this before
gay marriage started happening in big
numbers Lakers were winning
championships that's all I'm saying
Larry Wilmore here if you like the
nightly show on Comedy Central like us
on Facebook too just don't poke me I do
not like being poked you can Candy Crush
me